preview of the next issue
From our junior
From Ms. Iginari Tohoku
Karen Tachibana
Hello.
I was wondering what you were doing because there are some people left.
And when I looked, Karen was there.
You were doing an insta-live earlier.
I saw that and thought I had no choice but to come.
And then I heard from her.
More than us.
There were more people there than us.
I was so surprised.
They're just regular people walking around.
You're here, too, right?
May I?
You want me to go?
Karen, take the lead.
I'll take care of it.
There are a lot of tourists from overseas, aren't there?
Yes, we do.
I see a lot of them.
May I?
Hello.
Hello. - Hello.
It's okay.
And you?
I'm good.
What about you?
Beef tongue idol
Yay!
You are
Top Smile Idol
Yay
Thank you
Seino
Please enjoy Japan
Thank you
Bye
You're so cute!
I'm so happy for you.
I can't believe we're talking.
That's what I'm talking about.
Karen.
I mean, it's like we just bumped into each other.
Thank you very much.
You're very light on your feet, aren't you?
I'll have to come.
You've been here a long time.
And you, Karen...
How many times have you been to the tailgate?
With my family.
We come here to hang out.
Often.
I come here a lot.
It's my favorite place.
I'm glad that Lily came.
I'm glad you're here.
Thank you very much.
When we played with the people of Onaga-ya
When we had a live performance.
At the event.
Karen came to see us.
I really appreciate it.
It was a good opportunity for me to be scouted.
Seven years ago
That's amazing.
I have a lot of feelings for you.
What a surprise.
You've grown up to be such a big boy.
You and your son
Look how big they've grown.
Karen from home.
Oh, my God.
Today, Karen and
Ms. Okamoto and I...
I'd like to take a walk with you.
That's right.
This is where the name
It's engraved here.
Takagi's too.
Takagi's too, right?
Yes, it does.
Yes, I heard so.
A fan said so.
He said so.
Really?
It's around here.
There it is?
That way?
There it is.
Momo Kuro, they're all here.
That's right.
Ta-da!
Lenny Tagaki!Tagaki Renee
Located in room 606
Room 606
Room 606.
This is amazing.
Wear a car.
Arin.
The heat's strong.
It's everywhere.
Lenny's fans.
They're all coming to touch it.
They'll touch it.
Come on, guys.
Wow.
I'm glad I got to see that.
I'm so glad.
So many names.
Okay, let's go inside.
Yes, sir.
Beach terrace.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
I want to eat everything.
It's good, isn't it?
They're all so cute.
So cute.
Cute?
The food samples are amazing.
That's it.
I can't believe I'm wearing that.
But it's amazing.
Can I get a sea squirt?
I love it!
You want to try some?
Can I try some?
That's a great ascidian egg.
Hello.
I'm Irocloisette.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
boiled egg
Amazing.
Delicious!
handmade
Delicious.
It's amazing.
It tastes like a sea squirt.
It tastes like a sea squirt, but with the sweetness of an egg.
Wow, it's delicious!
It's really good.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
What's this?
What's that over there?
Thank you very much.
I've had it before.
You've had it before?
When I had it before.
They were advertising "kobugaki" at the movies.
It was so delicious.
I'll have some.
It's called "kobugaki".
In front of me
Wow, what a nice expression!
This is the kind of food that goes well with rice and sake!
It's true!
This is...
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
It's so plump.
Thank you very much.
It's hard to find a texture like this.
Delicious.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you very much.
So delicious!
I think I'll buy some ascidian roe too!
This place is
Newly opened!
It's called Koneiwa Burger.
Amazing!
Koeiwa Burger!
Delicious!
The main item here is the Koyeiwa Burger!
Salmon!
The best Western-style Ginza restaurant in Japan!
Fried salmon.
The patties are instead
Absolutely delicious!
Let's eat.
I'll have three of the Onegama burgers, please.
Yes, please.
Thank you very much.
Okay, well, let's wait a bit.
In front of Takase-san.
In front of Takase-san.In front of Mr. Takase.
Ah, it's Mr. Takase.
It's Takase-san.
It's our sales floor.
Hello.
But every time Takase-san comes, he comes back with a new menu.
What's that?
What is it?
It's that new persimmon, isn't it? I'm sure.
There were still some left, right?
That's right. This one.
Persimmon.
I got a little bit of a persimmon feeling, and somehow I got the Emperor's Cup.
That's amazing. The Emperor's Cup, for what it's worth.
Wow. Oh no.
Is this a limited time offer?
Oh, my God, it's on sale.
Oh no.
If it's not sold out.
Oh, I see. I want to buy some and take them home.
That's right.
But I eat Takahata-san's fish cakes all the time in private.
I see. I see.
I wonder if it was made with light dough.
I had that the other day and it was really delicious.
It was one of Karen's favorites.
The cheese is so rich and delicious.
Highly recommended.
It's amazing.
It's all delicious.
It was here earlier.
What?
Wait. I want to buy some to take home.
What? I'm sure.
There's sea urchin, too.
Two persimmons and two sea urchins.
And two Awayuki cheeses.
Thank you very much.
Yay! Got it!
Now let's see what's inside.
Yo!
Open!
Wow! It's huge!
It's huge!
What?
Wait.
What's going on here? Isn't it amazing?
It's so jumpy.
It's so shiny here.
The bread is so chewy.
The buns are a little different from the buns you get at the chain restaurants, aren't they?
Yes, it is.
Let's all eat together.
Wow, this volume.
It's a joy to open.
It's a very delicious-looking Onaga Burger.
I've heard of it.
Wow, this tartar is also overflowing with tartar.
I'm going to eat it with a big hearty appetite.
Yum!
So delicious!
Everything is delicious.
I knew this beautiful woman was good.
Salmon?
She's young, isn't she?
Young?
Did you hear? You just said she's nice.
She's nice.
You know what I mean? What?
She's visually appealing.
Well, not yet in our generation.
Youth.
Yummy!
Delicious!
So crispy!
Freshly fried?
Amazing!
I knew it. We're in a port town.
Using local silver salmon
Freshly fried and crispy
As crispy as possible.
It's deep fried, but freshly fried
Mmmm
Because this is salmon.
The flavor of salmon is
It's a new sensation.
You know what I mean? I've never had it before.
It's amazing. It's really, really good.
It's delicious.
Mmm.
Great, great, great, great! We're here!
We landed before we knew it!
We didn't fly, but we landed!
So, you know, we really tasted the gourmet food of Onagawa!
It was delicious! I'm so full!
What's next?
We ate a lot of delicious food, so after that, we should have some fun.
Spanish tiles in Onagawa, Minatomachi Ceramica Kobo!This is the Port Town Ceramica Studio, a Spanish tile studio in Onagawa!
We are going to have a tile painting experience here!
Sounds like a lot of fun!
You can eat good food and have fun just around the station and other places, it's amazing!
It's fun!
Nice tiles!
What do you think? Do you have a good artistic sense, Karen?
Your artistic sense is something unique!
Oh, you're being smitten!
I see! I'm looking forward to it!
Well then, let's work a little harder, while Takahashi-san judges us!
Please do!
Okay, let's go!
Here you go!
Thank you very much.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Nice to meet you.
Wow, this is amazing.
So many cute tiles!
Oh, they're so nice!
I didn't know they had clocks and clocks.
There's even a nameplate!
So cute!
I didn't know tiles had so many designs until now.
I didn't know there were so many designs.
So cute!
I didn't know you could do this.
Let's make our own unique tiles today!
Let's make the one and only original tile in the world.
Please do.
I think I'll go with the phone design.
Yes, of course.
This is what I'd like to have.
I wonder if there was a price on the front pub last time~.
You all have a great day!
See you in the next video below.
Bye!
Sorry, great, I forgot the camera was rolling.
Of course it was.
You scared the shit out of me.
I'm so surprised now. Go back to yourself.
I'm seriously in my own world right now.
I'm sorry, he said he was here today for a photo shoot.
I'm so surprised.
I've got it.
Here it is.
Here's my draft.
It's amazing!
It's a picture of a fish and a friend of Nagaawa's.
Here's a picture of a person and the word "love" and...
And a clover in black and white.
I wrote a clover to signify a friend.
Ta-da!
What do you think of Nakaren-chan?
I think I saw a little bit of her...
What an impact!
I had a hard time deciding...
But when I came to Ochowa today...
I was really impressed by Reni-chan's smile next to me and the warmth of the Ochowa.
and the warmth and smiling face of Ochowa.
I felt so happy this time.
I wrote a smile on my face to express that I was happy with everything.
I wrote a smiley face to express that I was happy with all of them.
Is this a self-portrait of Karen?
Korena-chan.
Me?
Is this me?
It's a little more...
You've got a cute voice.
Thank you for watching.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's like arts and crafts time.
I understand.
What was your favorite subject, Karin?
My favorite subject?
But I really like home economics and arts and crafts.
That's good.
I'm having fun today.
What kind of a student were you, Karin?
I was very shy.
Really?
Yes, really.
I don't feel like it.
Except for one girl friend, I was always using honorifics for about three years.
What?
That's right.
Isn't that amazing? You must be good friends.
Yes, we are.
Surprising.
Really?
I was surprised because you are always smiling at me whenever I see you.
What kind of girl was Rene-chan?
I wonder what kind of girl she was.
Yes.
I think she was a hell of a girl.
I could do it.
Yes, I could do it. It's done.Yes, I have done it. I was able to do it.
But I, I was able to do it like that, wasn't I?
I was able to do it too.
The oil component in the lead of that mechanical pencil is the bank that stops this liquid.
If the line is too thin, this paint will stick out.
So, in order to stop it firmly, you need to draw a thick line.
Yes, I did that.
Great.
This is
I'm curious.
What is he doing?
Like the ultimate laundry game.
What's that?
I'd like to ask you, Karina.
Will you have nose hairs for the rest of your life?
Or would you rather have ear hairs for the rest of your life?
Which would you prefer?
This is the first time I've been asked.
If I cut it off, it would explode.
I guess I'd rather have ears.
Ears.
I like ear hair too.
Because I can be one with my twin-tails.
So this is the kind of conversation you have?
Yes, we do. This is how we talk.
That's nice.
What do you have in mind? A subject.
Of course. I don't know if I have anything.
What would you take with you to a deserted island?
What's that?
Not the ultimate laundry?
That's a question.
What would you take to a deserted island?
I see. I have to choose between two options.
If you're taking something to a deserted island.
I have to choose between food and a cell phone.
Ah. I see.
Cell phones.
Why?
I'll die if I don't have a cell phone.
But it will run out of charge, right?
That's right.
I'm done.
It's difficult.
But shortly.
Kya.
How are you feeling, Karin?
Will you be ready soon, Karin?
Soon.
Gogo Karen.
Oh!
I'm so happy!
Gan Gan Karen!
I'll do my best.
That's it.
You're seeing through me.
No!
She said it's a translucent thing.
It's like you're happy.
No!
Finish yourself.
You're so cute.
Oh, 20 seconds!
Ten seconds.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Two.
OK!
Ray's colors are so pretty!
It's kinda like a pastel!
It's so pretty!
I'll put it on.
Oh, I got it, I got it! That's great!
Shake it like this!
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh, that's good!
That's good!
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Like it!
Nice!
Now I'm wearing Rina's lipstick.
Hold it pretty.
I'll take care of it.
Oh, no.
The teacher was whispering, "Good job!
So cute.
I did it!
I did it! It's done!
Wow! It's so cute!
Oh, wow!Oh, wow!
Onagaawa love!
How satisfied are you?
Well, it was a little difficult to draw the details.
But I was able to draw a good balance of "Onagawa love," so I gave it an 86.
I gave it 86 points.
The sports around here are also good.
Another perfect score.
Oh, wow!
The teacher is too kind.
Tachibana also made it.
Did you do it?
I did!
Amazing!
What do you think? How do you like it, Reni-chan?
It's really good!
It has an impact!
I feel like I'm in a dream!
Indeed.
Cute, but...
But it's cute! I think I was able to express the cuteness.
I hope this reminds everyone of Ririe-chan's smile and the goodness of Onagawa.
Wow!
Is this what it looks like after baking?
So, we have successfully completed it.
When it is finished, it will look like this.
I'll be able to see the belly in front of Onagawa Station.
I'm so happy. I'm so happy.
So I really hope you will come to Onagawa, eat delicious food, and see the tiles we made.
I hope you will come to Onagawa, eat delicious food, and look at the tiles we made.
And now, a replica of our design is going to be sold.
This?
We didn't think we'd be selling them either.
We were pretty excited about it, but we put a lot of love and effort into it.
But we put a lot of love into it.
We made it with a lot of love, and we made it while it was still shiny.
We hope you enjoy the design as much as we did.
So, I enjoyed my day in Onagawa.
I have been to Onagawa many times, but every time I come here
I have been to Onagawa many times, but every time I come here, I discover something new.
I think that is the depth of Onagawa.
I also feel the warmth of the people, the connections and
I am very happy to be able to feel the warmth of the people and their connection with each other.
I want to come back again.
I want to come again.
I would love to come back again, because we have been here several times.
We have been here a few times, but we were too busy to keep up with the ever-evolving city.
Every time we come here, there are new stores and new places to experience.
We have new shops and corners where you can experience things like this, so we are still friends.
We still feel that we haven't done enough for being friends, so we are going to keep coming back.
So, even though we are still friends, we haven't done anything yet, so there is still a gap between us.
But we will continue to do it with the same kindness.
We are still in the midst of a gap, but we will continue to do our best with the same kindness.
I thought it was very nice that they would tell us about the town and give us updates on what's going on.
I thought I would like to cherish that kind of thing again.
I hope to come back to Onagawa with you again in the future.
I hope you and Karin will come back again.
I want to tell people about the charm of Onagawa, of course.
I want to tell people about the charms of Onagawa, of course, but first of all, I want to enjoy it myself.
I would like to experience it all by myself first.
I see that President Takatani has returned to his work since he is busy.
But now that you are back here too, I thought you might like to see the tiles we designed.
How do you like the tiles we designed?
Fans won't be able to resist.
Fans will love it.
By the way, do you know who this illustration designed by
Who do you think it is?
I think it's probably Eni-chan, right?
How do you know?
I know exactly who it is.
No way!
I'm happy, but not happy.
That's why I'm happy about this one, too.
Please put it up.
I will definitely display it.
Thank you very much.
I put a lot of my feelings for Onagawa and my thoughts about Onagawa into this work, so I
I can feel it.
I usually have the opportunity to come here for events and so on.
It's not often that I get a chance to experience
or taste delicious food at a leisurely pace.
Talking with Mr. Takamasa and other people in the community
It's not often that we get to talk about memories of the past with Mr. Takamasa or local people.
It's not often that we get to talk about our memories with Mr. Takamasa or other local people.
But today was almost like a photo shoot.
It's almost like it's a private event.
It was so much fun that I forgot the camera was rolling.
I had so much fun that I forgot about it.
I felt like I was able to experience Onagawa.
It was a lot of fun.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
I thought you guys looked like you were having a great time.
I wish you guys could see Onagawa as it really is.
It's not just me.
There are probably a lot of people who live in Onagawa.
I'd like to show them how much fun we had today.
I want everyone to see it again.
Momoguro and Onagawa.
Tohoku-san and Onagawa.
And as the other sideAnd as the other side of the story
I'm sure we'll be able to bring you another side of the story.
I hope you will see it.
We are also friends with Onagawa
We are friends with Onagawa and we became a bridge between the two.
But Onagawa was the catalyst for us to do this.
Tohoku, and suddenly we were able to build bridges with Tohoku.
I feel as if we have connected many bridges.
I'm very happy.
I'd like to hold a joint event.
Please do!
In Onagawa
I'd love to do it sometime.
I'd love to!
Thank you so much for today!
Thank you very much.
Everyone come to Onagawa!
See you soon!
Come again!
Come again.
You look just like him.
Do I look like him? Do I look like him?
Do I look like him?
Come and see our tiles.
Konaga is love!